<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Editorials>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Lindsey-Vonn-For-Rhapsody-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/LindseyVonn</ImageDirectory>
    <HeaderTitle>Lindesy Vonn Editorial Shoot For Rhapsody Magazine</HeaderTitle>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Fashion Photographer, and Editorial Photographer who shot Lindsey Vonn for Rhapsody Magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based editorial Photographer Dave Brown worked with Rhapsody Magazine for a piece in their upcoming issue about overcoming adversity.</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, Lindsey Vonn</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divLindseyVonn</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup>
     <![CDATA[ 
     <h1>Lindsey Vonn for the cover of Rhapsody Magazine</h1>
      <p>
          I had an awesome opportunity to shoot Lindsey Vonn for an editorial in Rhapsody Magazine. I was super excited to get to work with my first big star, and we got some amazing shots for the magazine.
      </p>
      <p>
          I was actually down in Austin when I got the call that Rhapsody wanted me to shoot their cover story. I kinda freaked out a little bit. It actually took me a little while before I was convinced that I could handle the job. I had to call a few people to convince me I'd be crazy not to take a cover story.
      </p>
      <p>
          After working out all the details for the shoot I agreed to show up a bit early to do some location scouting. We were shooting at the Ritz Carlton in Vail. Which was an amazing place. I can only imagine how expensive it is to live there. The early part of the morning was spent walking around with the creative director on set, talking through what they would want to do with the shots. The mood that they were going for. They wanted it to be more of a fashion shoot with warm lighting, perfect for my style.
      </p>
      <p>
          I had never worked on a project this big. Hair, makeup, wardrobe stylist, writer, creative director, photography editor, assistants, handlers, it was a huge ordeal. Which probably explains why we started so late. That's ok, though I think some of my favorite shots from the shoot only happened because we started so late.
      </p>
      <p>
          We started the day in her own gondola. I know crazy right? She's got her own gondola, that they put on the line just for her, and this shoot. I have to say when the shoot started I was a bit worried. We started shooting, and I didn't feel any connection from her. She seemed pretty good at posing, and stuff, but there wasn't much of a connection. To her, this was just another shoot. She had 3 that day alone.
      </p>
      <p>
          Once we got in the gondola though it was a totally different story. I got to ask her about the broncos game she had gone to the night before, and suddenly she opened up. We talked about how hard it is to not drink any beer, because at the time she was training hard for the Olympics, but she was funny and energized, and a total doll to work with.
      </p>
      <p>
          After the gondola, we moved onto shooting in one of the giant suites at the Ritz. To say the place was gorgeous was an understatement. We had a blast putting her in all different kinds of outfits and getting interesting looks out of her.
      </p>
      <p>
          At the end we did some shots in a makeshift studio. They were thinking they were going to use those ones for the cover, but we ended up going in a different direction. They ended up using some of the sunset shots, which I totally loved for the cover.
      </p>
      <p>
          Overall I was extremely happy with the way the shoot went, and I certainly learned plenty about being under that kind of pressure. It was a complete blast to shoot something that big, and I'm excited for the next time I get to work on a shoot that big.
      </p>
      ]]>
  </Writeup>
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Wanderlust-For-Ellements-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/Wanderlust</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who shot Two Models for the cover photography of Ellements Magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Ellements magazine to put together a fun summer editorial that featured two well known models.</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, Wanderlust, Sun, Fashion</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divWanderlust</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup>
      <![CDATA[ 
     <h1>Wanderlust Editorial for Ellements Magazine</h1>
      <p>
      I was so excited to shoot this editorial.  I had this editorial in my head for a very long time.  It was something that I just needed to get out of my head.  I was super excited to get to work with such a great team.  I knew that I was going to have 2 fantastic models, for this shoot, but I went with someone new for Hair and makeup.  Which I was super happy with, and it turned out that this was the makeup artist first publication.  Which was totally awesome.  I love it when people are firts published with my work.
      </p>
      <p>
      For my models I picked 2 girls that I had worked with before, people I knew I could count on.  A shoot as I say is always made by the weakest link in the team.  So picking models that you trust, and you know will 'bring it' on the day of a shoot makes the whole shoot easier.  
      </p>
      <p>
      I started out location scouting in Red Rocks park.  Which I have to say I wasn't exactly the best little camper ever.  I didn't exactly stay on the trails, and I managed to find a really cool location that was a bit off the trail.  Of course you're not exactly supposed to go back there, but I thought it would be ok.  More on that later. :)
      <br />
      After red rocks park I moved on to do some location scouting around there.  I found a cool location that seemed to be the start of a hiking trail, but was also what seemed to be an abandoned road, a shed that was trashed. 

      I also managed to find some cool park like locations that weren't actually in the red rocks park... boy did those come in handy.  Again more on that later.
      </p>
      <p>
      We started the day off with hair and makeup with Samantha Koch.  The girls got ready quickly.  After that me and one of the model who had also done some of the styling starting picking out exactly what clothes we were going to put together for this shoot.  I wanted a bit bohemian, but also a bit edgy.  Once we had all the looks picked out, and the girls hair was ready, we were ready to go.
      </p>
      <p>
	      The first location was probably the funniest.  And hence why I wanted to wait and tell you guy s about it.  So we went to Red Rocks, a bit off of the beaten path.  Not exactly legal, but we were behind a bunch of huge rocks so I figured nobody could see us.  We'd be fine.  Right?  Apparently not.  A while into shooting a few park rangers showed up and quickly scolded us for being where we shouldn't be.  They weren't exactly happy about us jumping a fence to get to where we were shooting.  They asked us to specifically show them exactly how we got to our location.  They were expecting us to show them that we jumped a fence, but I was way ahead of them.  I had already found a location in the fence where it had a nice gap, something that could be construed to look like an opening.  After showing them that they were forced to simply give us a warning, and direct me to talk to the person who was in charge of booking shoots on the property.  I kinda felt bad the whole time they were scolding us, because one of the models was wearing a see through shirt with no bra on, and wasn't exactly comfortable having a 25 year old park ranger stare at her in a leering way.  
      </p>
      <p>
	      After that whole experience we moved pretty quickly through the rest of the shoot.  We relocated to another public park that seemed to have a lot less restrictions on where all you could go.  In the end I was actually quite happy that the park rangers kicked us out of Red rocks.  It made me shoot more in the other public park, and in the end I had some gorgeous light to work with, and I was really happy with the way those shots turned out.
      </p>
      <p>
	      After all that I moved on to my abandoned location.  Which was great, the light was just barely peeking through the corner of the mountians, and it came off amazingly well on camera.  In the end the shot where the model is posing implied with just a jacket over her, is quite possible in my top 5 shots of all time.  Frankly it wasn't even my idea.  It was the other models idea, and boy did I love it.  
      </p>
      <p>
	      After the shoot I knew I had some magical shots, and I wanted to aim high, and that's why I was very careful where I submitted my images to.  I sent them around to aim as I high as I thought was realistic, and ended up having them published in ellements magazine.  Of course I was stupid proud and happy about that fact.
      </p>
      ]]>
    </Writeup>
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Inheritance-For-Modo-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/Inheritance</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who shot for Modo Magazine in Osaka, Japan</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Tokyo, based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Modo magazine to put together a fun foriegn editorial for Modo Magazine</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Osaka, Denver, Tokyo, Japan, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, Inheritance, Fashion</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divWanderlust</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup>
      <![CDATA[ 
     <h1>Inheritance Editorial for Modo Magazine</h1>
      <p>
      This shoot was an absolute blast. I got to work with a gorgeous model in Osaka, Japan to put together some really amazing shots.  I loved
      the way the print edition of this editorial came out.
      </p>
      ]]>
    </Writeup>
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Just-Let-Go-For-Modo-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/JustLetGo</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who shot for Huf Magazine in Tokyo, Japan around the Shinjuku area</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Tokyo, based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Huf magazine to put together a fun fashion editorial for Huf Featuring an internation model Yurina @ Bellona Agency</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Osaka, Denver, Tokyo, Japan, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, Just Let Go, Fashion</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divWanderlust</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup>
      <![CDATA[ 
     <h1>Just Let Go Editorial for Huf Magazine</h1>
      <p>
      This was another fantastic shoot that I did on my last trip to Tokyo Japan.  Again so much fun working with an amazing team of artists on this one.
      I think I really captured something fantastic with this shoot.
      </p>
      ]]>
    </Writeup>
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Lightdance-For-Fashion-Couture-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/Lightdance</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who luccia for fashion couture magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Fashion couture magazine to put together a creative lighting editorial with sam martucci and Luccia.</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, Lighdance, color, lighting</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divLightdance</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup>
	<![CDATA[
	  <h1>LightDance Editorial in LaDamme Magazine</h1>
    <p>
    This editorial was a ton of fun to work on.  Initially Luccia the model here sent me a shot that she wanted to use as a inspiration for the shoot.  The problem with the shots that she sent me, were that they were extremely good.  Not only were they good, they were complex with regards to lighting and I had no idea if I was going to be able to pull off this shoot.
    </p>
    <p>
    So for this shoot I actually worked for two weekends coming up with lighting for this shoot.  At first I thought it was done with a really long snoot and then putting slats over the end of the snoot.  At first I tried to use a tube from some of my paper rolls to build the really long snoot.  It was very obvious after I spent an hour building this thing that this was not what I needed.  
    </p>
    <p>
    I started doing some more research and thinking through how you can create the sharpest shadows.  For this shoot I wanted the edges of the shadows to be really hard.  I tried to do something where I put my lights up really high, and then far away and I put something right in front of the wall to create the shadows, but I couldn't push enough light through the scrim to create the shadows that I wanted.
    </p>
    <p>
    After that didn't work, I had to go back to the drawing board.  So I decided to try something else.  I had read that I needed to focus the light.  All the rays needed to be going in one direction.  It couldn't be a spray of light.  Well apparently what I was looking for was a profoto light that did this.  At the end of the studio strobe it has a lens on it that does this.  This is called a fresnal lens.  Of course these things aren't cheap, and I certainly wasnt' going to spend that kind of money on a single shoot.  Also I couldn't see myself using this light on another shoot. 
    </p>
    <p>
    So to get a light that would actually focus the light, I decided to use an overhead projector.  The way that these work is by having a giant fresnal lens in them.  This focuses the light so that when you create shadows or write on them, they show up clearly.
    </p>
    <p>
    So after I got the light figured out, I called up the team, and we figured out how to get a shoot pulled together.  We ended up getting a great makeup artist in Natosha Cooke, and Luccia is of course a fantastic model.  We also pulling in a local designer to get some interesting pieces to go along with the shoot.  The only trick was the fact that the light was using was actually quite dim, meaning that I had to keep luccia quite still otherwise I would get a ton of blur in those shots.  I had to work hard to get crisp clean shots. It ended up being a great editorial photoshoot.  This is what I love about being a denver photographer.  
    </p>
	]]>
	</Writeup>
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Firestarter-For-IMute-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/Firestarter</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who shot Eva for IMute Magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Fashion couture magazine to put together a shoot about a bad girl walking through the streets.</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, Sunlit, lighting, sunset</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divFirestarter</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup>
      <![CDATA[ 
        <h1>Firestarter Editorial in IMute Magazine</h1>
        <p>
        So the funny thing about this editorial wasn't that I had some big grandious plan for it, it was actually the complete opposite.  In reality this was test work that just turned into an editorial.  I hadn't even planned on doing anything with these shots, but then after the shoot I was amazed at how gorgeous eva looks, and I knew that I wanted to get them published somewhere.  Now I didn't exactly do a great job shooting this like an editorial.  I didn't pull amazing clothes, or anything crazy.  Hell I just barely went location scouting for this shoot. 
        </p>
        <p>
	        We started out at my studio close to downtown.  Of course I had the usual team: me, Lynzi, Kadie, and of course Eva, and her absolutely fantastic mother.  I have a bit of a crush on Eva's mom.  She's hilarious, and I really wish I would have grown up with a mother like that.  Sounds like Eva's dad is pretty funny too.  Their whole family is fantastic.  This was my first time working with Eva, and I was so wildly impressed.  She's an amazing model, and a total blast to work with.  She's a complete goofball.  It makes the shooting go so much easier.  It's also so much easier to be creative when you're working with fun people and you have a smile on your face
        </p>
        <p>
	        After we got out to our location we started shooting and immediatly I knew this was going to be a great shoot.  Eva has fantastic movements.  Combined with the fact that she's drop dead gorgeous.  It was truly easy to shoot her.  We honestly put together a whole editorial quite easily just shooting one location.  What I did was try and use one small location in as many ways as I could.  To do this I chose to shoot all the different kinds of light the location had, along with using some artificial light to create even more drama in the shots.
        </p>
        <p>
	        For all the natural light photographs we went for that warm drenched look that I love so much.  I shot with a ton of rear lighting which was complicated when I first started shooting like that, but over time I found that this was my favorite style, and now it's fully integrated into my photography.  
        </p>
        <p>
	        After I got done shooting the natural light stuff, I brought out some of my strobes for even more drama in the shots.  I used a beauty dish in the shade with barely any power behind it.  I also used a neutral density filter to drop my exposure even further, and yet still be able to use a wide open aperture.  Now you can see in the shots that I really didn't have to add very much light, because it's really not needed to put a ton of punch into a photo.
        </p>
      ]]>
    </Writeup>
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Milan-On-My-Lips-For-Raine-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/MilanOnMyLips</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who shotfor Raine Magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Raine Magazine magazine to put together a shoot with a bit of love and nostalgia.</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, clothes, fashion, couture</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divMilan</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup>
		<![CDATA[ 
		<h1>Milan on my lips Editorial in Raine Magazine</h1>
		<p>
		This really was a blast of an editorial to work on.  There was a model who was in town from milan, and I knew that I had to work with her while she was here.  She had a feature in Nylon, and if that wasn't enough she had a fantastic look to her, and she seemed like she would be a fun model to work with.  I had seen the caliber of photographer that she had worked with, and I won't lie, I was a bit intimidatted.  It's hard to shoot someone who has worked with any big name photographers, because they can be a bit snooty.  Emory wasn't at all, she was awesome to work with, and even put up with my team going on and on about various boys and other crap in the backseat of my car.   
		</p>
		<p>
		I knew I wanted to put together a fun summer editorial.  So I wanted to get a full team together for this shoot.  I went location scouting in some new places which was a ton of fun.  And I found some great spots for us to get some killer shots.  I even tried to get into this old junkyard.  I met some good old boys who basically told me no.  Which didn't stop me from trying some more, which is why I ended up jumping a fence to take a look around this old junkyard.  There were some really old cars in there which were cool to look at, but sadly you can't ask a signed agency model to trespass for your submission editorial.  They get a bit pissy about that.  Well actually I guess it's their agent that would get pissy about that.    
		</p>
		<p>
		Of course though the colorado weather is wildly unpredictable in the summer time.  Which always kinda pisses me off.  Dear colorado can you for once not rain at 5pm?  That would be great thanks.  Of course for this shoot that didn't happen and it started to pour on us half way through the shoot.  I was really worried that the look of the shots from half being in natural light, and half being in the studio wouldn't work.  And frankly there were a lot of publications that turned this editorial down. 
		</p>
		<p>
		I kept trying though, and eventually this editorial got picked up by more of a major publication than I thought, like a real publication that has real print runs.  Which was awesome.  The publication rain in Raine magazine.  Which was great seeing as how I had actually put a lot of work into these shots.  
		</p>
		<p>
		For the studio shots I ended up using a ringlight on white, which it might sound like that wouldn't work, but it's become one of my favorite setups for getting really great looking shots.  Hell I even recently used it on a model test, and the shots came out fantastic.  
		</p>
		<p>
		My shots on black with natural light have become one of my staples.  I love the way they look, and they put the focus right where it should be, on the model, and her clothes.
		</p>
      ]]>
    </Writeup>
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Star-Collector-For-IMute-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/StarCollector</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer who shot Zoe Myers for a fashion editorial in Imute Magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Imute Magazine to put together an editorial of summer fun and care free</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, summer, sun, care free, star, collector</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divStarCollector</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup>
      <![CDATA[ 
		  <h1>Star Collector Editorial for IMute Magazine</h1>
		  <p>
      The funny thing about this editorial is that it didn't start off that way at all.  At first I was just trying to shoot some great test work for Zoe.  Who is a local wilhelmina model.  I always enjoy working with girls like Zoe.  She has a great personality, and was super fun to work with.  Even though she hadn't worked with that many photographers, she managed to still move really well.   
      </p>
      <p>
      We started off the shoot working in my backyard basically.  Well the backyard to my studio.  I like the light out there when you catch it at the right time.  Normally everyone is drawn to all the grafitti on the walls, but honestly I think it's so trite to shoot against the graffiti, unless you just use it for fun colors.  I think it's just been done far too often to shoot against it.  Instead I prefer my editorials to have a new york, or LA vibe to them.  That's why I make sure to stay away from things like train tracks, or mountains.  Well I guess the mountains can be fun to shoot against, but certainly not for a majority of my editorials.
      </p>
      <p>
      After we got done shooting out in my backyard, we ran out to a location that I was super stoked on.  It's nothing special to look at, but I could see it had potential.  It's actually the old stockyards.  Nothing too crazy, but there are some cool abandoned areas.  Something I always manage to love shooting.  I think part of it has to do with the fact that I like doing my photography in secluded areas.  Nobody likes an audience.  The problem was that when we got there the light wasn't good yet.  It was still too bright outside for me.  So I went to a backup location
      </p>
      <p>
      My backup location ended up being some of my favorite shots.  Something I'm always shoked by.  It seems like when you're shooting editorials like these you have a specific thought in your head, and then when you change it, you think you're going to be disapointed, but that wasn't the case here.  In fact these were some of the best shots of the day.  I always forget how great it can look to get a bit of what boils down to bard door light when the sun falls behind another building.  That's what happened here.
      </p>
      <p>
      Even though we didn't really have enough clothes to make a backup location work, in the end it turned out great, because instead of just having shots for a test session, I ended up with enough shots for an editorial, which is awesome.  So sometimes when your plans don't quite turn out right, you have to go back and in the end it works out well for everyone.
      </p>
      <p>
      After my first few sets of shots we ended up finishing out the shoot on the roof of this old building, and I adored the way that those shots turned out.  All in all I'm really happy with the way this editorial turned out. 
      </p>
        ]]>
    </Writeup>
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Can-I-Stay-A-While-For-Jute-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/CanIStayaWhile</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who shot Kora Amundsen for a fashion set in Jute Magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Jute to put together a shoot with a seedy motel vibe</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, motel, seedy, sexy</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divCanIStayAWhile</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup />
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Pale-Fire-For-Glacier-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/PaleFire</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who shot Manda Lee Hesterly for Glacier Magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based Photographer Dave Brown worked with glacier to put together a shoot with a pretty girl on fire.</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, pale, fire</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divPaleFire</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup />
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Femme-Au-Foyer-For-Jute-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/FemmeAuFoyer</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who shot Megan Smith for Jute Magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Jute to put together a shoot about housewife who was tired of it all.</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, housewife, french, fashion</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divFemme</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup />
  </Editorial>
  <Editorial>
    <EditorialName>Never-Going-Home-For-Jute-Magazine</EditorialName>
    <ImageDirectory>Editorial/NeverGoingHome</ImageDirectory>
    <PageTitle>Dave Brown is a Denver Editorial Photographer Photographer who shot Madi for Jute Magazine</PageTitle>
    <MetaDescription>Denver, Colorado based Photographer Dave Brown worked with Jute to put together a shoot about a young runaway.</MetaDescription>
    <MetaKeywords>Denver, Editorial, Photogrpaher, Commercial, Print, Published, young, runaway, kid, fashion</MetaKeywords>
    <WriteupDivId>divNevergoinghome</WriteupDivId>
    <Writeup />
  </Editorial>
</Editorials>

